

Jusmin Lukan

Senior Front-End Developer

25a Belfort, Kragujevac, 554525, Serbia +381 (689) 251 3706 · <u>funnyGen1248@gmail.com</u>

Skills

React / Next.js / Redux

Vue.js / Nust.js / Vuex

AngularJS

Javascript / Typescript

GraphQL

CSS 3 / Bootstrap 5

Tailwind CSS

Semantic / Material - UI

Responsive & UI / UX

Hobbies

Badminton, Volleyball Skiing, Skating

Languages

English

Profile

I am a senior front-end developer with extensive experience specializing in developing and implementing the user interface (UI) and user experience (UX) of a website or application. I have advanced skills in React/Next, Vue/Nuxt, JS/TS and other web development technologies and strong leadership and communication skills. I can translate design mockups into functional, responsive web pages and manage multiple projects simultaneously. My role is providing an effective and engaging user experience that meets end-user needs and supports business goals.

Employment History

Senior Front-End Engineer, Jean Francois, Ontario

May 2022 - January 2023

- Created and implemented charming and interacting Betting Game UIs for decentralized betting site.
- Implemented smooth interaction between UI and Smart Contract using Web3.js.

Senior Front-End Developer, Charles, New York

March 2021 — February 2022

- Developed and launched chrome extension using React which collect product details from amazon and save them in database.
- Made postgreSQL database design and created a Backend server using Nest.js framework.

Senior Front-End Developer, Vertexplus, Singapore

October 2019 - March 2021

- Ensure efficient web development by supporting designers and app developers while resolving website performance issues.
- Designed dynamic and browser compatible pages using HTML5, CSS3, and React.js.

Senior Front-End Developer, Goreha, Kragujevac

September 2018 - April 2019

Led the front-end development of a multi-lingual digital rehabilitation platform.

- Used React and Redux to make the Reactive front end.
 - Migrated and merged an admin panel application into the platform.

Education

computer science, Technical School "15. maj", Kragujevac

October 2009 — September 2012

The school offers education programs in several technical fields, including mechanical engineering, electrical engineering, automotive engineering, and computer science.

Bachelor of Engineering, Kragujevac University, Kragujevac

October 2012 — September 2016

University of Kragujevac is a modern education and research center embracing almost all major areas of teaching and research, with a student population of 18.000 and 1.200 academic staff.